MOSES NWIGBERI

WEB/IOS DEVELOPER



- +234 807 548 9363
- mosesnwigberi@gmail.com
- Cooperation villas estate, Badore, Ajah. Lagos.
- themoeportfolio.vercel.app

PROFILE

Hello, I am a web and software developer with 2+ years of experience in software and web developement. I create functional web applications with the latest web technologies. I possess strong creative, analytical and time management skills. Team player with an eye for detail.

SKILLS

- Web Design and development.
- SEO optimization
- Mobile development(iOS)
- Problem-Solving
- Computer Literacy
- Time management
- Strong Communication

EXPERIENCE

FRONT END WEB DEVELOPER

ZZDIGITAL

2020-2022

- Web design and development.
- Updating and maintaining web user interfaces.
- Turned designs to functional web pages

FRONT END IOS DEVELEOPER ZZDIGITAL

2020-2021

- Collaborated with the iOS and Design teams turning client's designs to functional User Interfaces and developing the front end of a mobile software project with Swift.
- Learned Swift on the job

FREELANCE

2022- present

• Creating side and projects and freelancing.

EDUCATION

SECONDARY SCHOOL

EBSU staff secondary school **2011-2017**

CHEMICAL ENGINEERING

University of Lago, Akoka 2018-present